Hey friend, if you also work in an insurance company, then you become
an advisor or an agent,
okay, and you also have to switch to another company,
or you have reached a place
where you have to cancel your license,
okay, so what is the process for that? Let me
tell you, I have already made a
video about it, but I get a lot of
queries, due to which I felt that I should give a
little more clarity about what all happens. So
before that, the first thing we
need to do is
email our branch manager.
Please do not talk verbally,
whatever it is with your branch manager, you should
email it to your branch manager.
What will happen by emailing is that you will have a
written statement in the email that you have
followed the process. Then
what does the branch manager do? After receiving the email, they
give the process number
and send this email to the bank.
So the idea is something like this: when you
get your email, they start your cashless court
process.
Without NIC, the ROB will
not cancel your code. Okay, so
your first priority is to
get the NIC from your branch manager and
force the branch manager to do it as soon as possible
and send the NIC ID. Now, the ROB
processes it on its side, so
whatever code you have, the
time period is 90 days.
[Music]
So it will not be fast. If you are
going on the story, then mostly your
NIC copy is
that you have already submitted the cancellation of the court
because every insurance company